我们要做一个 Todo 应用，但这个应用不是 Todon，
We're gonna make a Todo app, but this app is Todon't,
我们会有想要停止的习惯。
we're gonna have habits that we wanna stop.
如果我们运行它，它会打开一个小的 webpack 服务器并且
And if we run this, it's gonna open up a little web pack server and
我们有 Todo 应用模板欢呼。
we have The Todo app template hurray.
因此，如果您查看该应用程序，它只是用于
So if you look at the app, it's just the standard template for
人们为他们的框架共享的 Todo 应用程序。
the Todo app that people share around for their frameworks.
我不想让人们不得不知道 React 进入这个领域，所以
And I didn't want people to have to know React coming into this, so
如果你在这里查看这个包，我们有我们的标准 HTML 包
if you look at this package here, we have our standard HTML package
这只是在样式表或 HTML 文件中加载包。
that's just loading the bundle in a style sheet, or HTML file.
但是我们也有这个 UI 文件夹，这是整个 UI，
But then we also have this UI folder and this is the entire UI,
它只是几个组件，我不想让您担心。
it's just a couple of components, and I don't want you to have to worry about it.
所以我只想说几件事，这样你就不必再看这个了。
So I just wanna call out a couple things so you don't have to look at this anymore.
所以我们有我们的初始渲染应用程序，它采用初始状态和
So we have our initial render app which takes an initial state and
一个调度函数。
a dispatch function.
所以我可以调出这个应用程序并让它重新渲染。
So I'm able to kinda call out of this app and have it rerender.
所以当我们进入调度函数时，它会被一个事件调用，
So when we go into the dispatch function, this gets called with an event,
所以这不是 Redux，它非常像 Redux，
so this is not Redux, it's very Redux-like,
这将被一个事件和一个有效载荷，一些数据调用。
that's gonna get called with an event and a payload, some data.
所以我们使用索引创建、销毁和查看，
So we get create, destroy with an index and view okay,
这些是我们仅有的事件，我们在这里有几个组件，
those are the only events we have, we've got a couple components in here,
并且对于这里的应用程序的其余部分来说真的不重要。
and should really be not important to the rest of the app here.
但我只想提一下，这就是在这里，你不需要了解 React。
But I just wanted to mention that this is here and you don't need to know React.
但是我们将在 app 下使用 state 和 dispatch。
But we're gonna cover under app with state and dispatch.
好的，回到索引，我们要在这里做什么
Okay, back to index, what we're gonna do here
就像我们之前对建模函数所做的一样。
is much like we did earlier with modeling functions.
我们要模拟这种还原过程，
We're gonna model this kind of reduction process,
因此，如果我启动应用程序，然后调用一些东西，则什么也不会发生。
so if I start off the app, and I call some stuff, nothing is happening.
所以当我们在这里被调用时，让我们继续记录，
So let's go ahead and log when we get called here,
我们将 console.log 操作和有效负载。
we'll console.log the action and the payload.
这是一天中我无法打字的时间
It's that time of day where I can't type, and
我必须在这里返回一些状态，可能是什么？
I have to return some state here as, probably what is it?
它期待返回所以事实上，让我把这个状态称为
It's expecting to return so in fact, let me just call this state so
我们做这件事后它不会爆炸。
it doesn't blow up after we do this thing.
所以我们有状态，我们会返回状态好的，
So we have state and we're gonna return state okay,
所以当我真的在这里做某事时
so when I actually do something here,
它说动作是创建，有效载荷被命名为 sdf。
it says the action is create and the payload is named sdf.
好吧，酷，我们可以这样做，一整天，我们得到这个动作，所以
All right, cool, we could do this, all day long, we get this action so
让我们构建一个小的创建操作来开始。
let's build a little create action just to start.
创建，我们暂时只在这里硬编码创建。
Create and we're just gonna hard code create in here for the time being.
所以这将需要有效载荷和状态，
So that would take the payload and the state,
有效载荷中的状态，有效载荷就是这个名字，所以
state in the payload and the payload being this name, so
我想这是我们习惯的名字，所以我们就叫这个习惯吧。
I guess this is the name of our habit, so let's just call this habit.
好的，我们要做的是对象分配，
All right, and what we're gonna do is object assign,
我们将用习惯返回新状态，
we're gonna return new state with the habit,
太好了，我们要用我们刚刚给它的这个习惯来覆盖以前的习惯。
great we're gonna overwrite the previous habits with this one that we just gave it.
所以我们用有效载荷调用 create 和
And so we call create with the payload and
状态，你只需返回那个。
the state, you just return that.
酷，美好的时光。
Cool, good times.
让我们看看会发生什么，我应该提到的一件事是我们
Let's see what happens, one thing I should should mention is we
必须再次渲染应用程序，就在此处使用新状态，好吗？
have to render the app again, right here with the new state, okay?
那么为什么我们不做一点事件循环来开始呢？
So why don't we make a little bit of an event loop just to start off?
我们把这个小事件叫做 appLoop，
Let's call this little event, it's called appLoop,
取一个初始状态，然后我们会做这种事情，
take an initial state, and then we'll do this kind of thing,
我们将称之为 appLoop，对吗？
and we'll call this appLoop, right?
所以它只是循环并呈现新状态调用我们的新状态
So it just loops around and renders the new the new state calls our
函数再次启动，然后我们可以摆脱这个状态变量和
function starts again, and then we can get rid of this state variable and
只需将其称为应用程序循环即可启动它。
just call it an app loop, to kick it off.
好的，你在我身边吗？
Okay, are you with me?
好的，让我们运行它并说，嗨，嘿，
All right, let's run this and say, hi, hey,
如果我点击它，它现在很酷，它消失了，这很有趣。
there it is cool now if I click it, it goes away that's fun.
因为我们没有创建，所以停止记录事件，
Because we don't have a create, so stop logging the event,
在这里，如果我们再次记录它，请记录操作和有效负载。
here, if we log it again, log the action and payload.
我们得到的是，如果我单击删除，我们将使用索引进行销毁，
We get is if I click the Delete we'll get a destroy with the index,
如果我单击实际标题，我将获得索引视图。
if I click the actual title, I'll get a view with the index.
这些是我们现在要在这个应用程序中处理的仅有的三个事件。
And those are the only three events we're going to handle in this app right now.
所以，我想我会把它们留在里面，所以我想我们已经
So, I guess I'll leave those in for a second, so I guess we had
构建另一个小路由器，所以我们要在动作上做路由。
build another little router, so what we gonna do route on the action.
我们只是将该函数称为状态负载，所以
We'll just call that function the state payload, so
再弄个小路由器，const route router，route [LAUGH] route，
get a little router again, const route router, route [LAUGH] route,
路由器，路由=。
router, route =.
那些是我们得到的三个函数或者我们得到的三个动作，
Those were the three functions that we got or the three actions we got,
我们只是将它们存根，因此 destroy 需要一个索引。
we'll just stub them out so destroy takes an index.
我们将不理会它
And we'll just leave that alone for
现在让我们清除它和视图，所以
now let's just clear it out and the view, so
这不是采用索引，而是采用带有索引属性的有效载荷，对吗？
this is not take in index this takes a payload with an index property, right?
所以我必须解构才能得到那个索引，不清楚为什么会这样？
So I'll have to destructure to get at that index, it's not clear why that's working?
好的，然后我们将继续查看这件事并
Okay, and then we'll go ahead and view the thing and
我们只想将当前索引设置为该索引，
we just wanna set the current index to that index,
因为它们被称为索引。
cuz they're called index.
我们想将页面设置为显示，我认为这称为显示，我们会弄清楚的。
And we wanna set the page to show, I think it's called show we'll figure it out.
太好了，看起来我们已经完成了，[笑] 看看会发生什么，AB，但是
Great, looks like we're done, [LAUGH] see what happens, A B, but
我们一次只保存一个我们实际上并没有附加任何东西。
we're only saving one at a time we're not actually appending anything.
如果我点击它嘿它说显示C，那很好，如果我删除怎么办？
If I click it hey it says showing C, that's good, what if I do delete?
它清除了它，我猜，[笑]所以
It clears it out, I guess, [LAUGH] so
我认为我们必须做的第一件事实际上是附加这个东西。
I think the first thing we have to do is actually append this thing.